A Guide to the Governor George C. Peery Executive records, 1934-1938
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Governor George C. Peery Executive records, 1934-1938
The Library of Virginia
23344b
56.70 cu. ft. (162 boxes)
Virginia. Governor (1934-1938: Peery)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Governor, January and May 1946.
Biographical Information
George Campbell Peery (1873-1952), from Tazewell County, served as governor from 17 January 1934 to 18 January 1938.
Scope and Content
The Executive Papers of Governor George C. Peery are housed in 162 boxes. The collection is arranaged into seven (7) series. Series have been designated for: I. General Correspondence. II. General Assembly. III. Reports on Audits. IV. Financial Affairs. V. Power Plants Maintenance. VI. Penal Affairs. VII. Federal Government. These records include applications, appointments, correspondence, extraditions, invitations, pardons, proclamations, reports, and requisitions. These records document the gubernatorial administration of George C. Peery from 17 January 1934 to 18 January 1938.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. General Correspondence
Series II. General Assembly
Series III. Reports on Audits
Series IV. Financial Affairs
Series V. Power Plants Maintenance
Series VI. Penal Affairs
Series VII. Federal Government
Contents List
- Series I. General Correspondence, 1934-1938., Extent: 46 cu. ft. [92 boxes]. (Box 1-92)
  The General Correspondence are housed in 92 boxes and are arranged alphabetically by topic. Subjects include: Adjutant General, Agriculture, Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Art Commission, Attorney General, Budget, Buildings and Grounds, Conservation and Development, Corporation Commission, Delegates Appointed for Meetings, Education, Fisheries, Health, Highways, Invitations, Judges, Law Enforcement, Miscellaneous Correspondence, Motor Vehicles, Old Age Pensions, Penitentiary, Proclamations, Public Welfare, Purchasing and Printing, Recommendations, Taxation, Unemployment Compensation Commission, Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, and George Washington (Houdon Statue).
  - Adjutant General (Box 1)
  - Adjutant General, 80th Division Reunion (Box 1)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Commissioner, Recommendations, Adams, Berkeley D. (Box 1-2)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Commissioner, Recommendations, Beck, C. Nelson (Box 2)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Commissioner, Recommendations, Connelly, L.B., Jr. (Box 2)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Commissioner, Recommendations, Glascock, Thomas B. (Box 2)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Commissioner, Recommendations, Halsinger, G.F. (Box 2)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Commissioner, Recommendations, Koimer, George W. (Box 2)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Commissioner, Recommendations, Wills, J.S. (Box 3)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Commissioner, Recommendations, Miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Board (Box 3)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Budget (Box 3)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Cotton (Box 3)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Dairy and Food Division (Box 3)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Lime Grinding Plant (Box 3)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Markets Division (Box 3)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Markets Division, Meek controversy (Box 3)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Potato situation (Box 3)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Tobacco (Box 4)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, Veterinarian (Box 4)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board (Box 4)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Battle, Col. Marion S. (Box 4)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Boscher, Albert O. (Box 4)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Brock, O.B. (Box 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Bruce W. Basil (Box 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Bullington, R. McC. (Box 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Cato, W.R. (Box 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Cox (Box 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Fugati, T.W. (Box 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Gilmer, Henry G. (Box 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Hoover, W.H. (Box 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Humphlett, J.J. (Box 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Johnson, C.E., Jr. (Box 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Keith, Mrs. Margaret N. (Box 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Langhorne, R.H. (Box 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, McWane, Fred W. (Box 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Martin, James C. (Box 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Mills, Wade M. (Box 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Morehead, F.H. (Box 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Sebrell, THomas E. (Box 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Spence, C. Aubrey, Jr. (Box 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Warwick, Peter C., Jr. (Box 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Whittle, Randolph G. (Box 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Appointments, Miscellaneous (Box 6-7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Budget (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Chamberlain Hotel matter (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Distillery controversy (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, General (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Law violations (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Requests for positions (Box 7-8)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Special police (Box 8)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Stores (Box 8)
  - American Art Exhibition (Box 8)
  - American Legion (Box 8)
  - American Legislators Association (Box 9)
  - Annual reports (Box 9)
  - Anonymous letters (Box 9)
  - Antietam celebration (Box 9)
  - Apple Blossom Festival (Box 9)
  - Appointments, Delegates (Box 9)
  - Appointments, Forest wardens (Box 9)
  - Appointments, Requiring confirmation (Box 9)
  - Appointments, Not requiring confirmation (Box 9)
  - Appointments, Staff (Box 10)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Box 10)
  - Armory Commission (Box 10)
  - Art Commission (Box 10)
  - Astor, Lady, Portrait (Box 10)
  - Attorney General, Recommendations (Box 10-11)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 11)
  - Autographs (Box 11)
  - Aviation (Box 11)
  - Aviation, Richmond Air Terminal (Box 12)
  - Better Business Bureau (Box 12)
  - Bonds (Box 12)
  - Boxing, Commission, Recommendations, Hamilton, CHarles H. (Box 12)
  - Boxing, Commission, Recommendations, Houston, Lem W. (Box 12)
  - Boxing, Commission, Recommendations, Roller, Charles S., Jr. (Box 12)
  - Boxing, Commission, Recommendations, Tullock, Jack (Box 12)
  - Boxing, Commission, Recommendations, Williams, C.R. (Box 12)
  - Boxing, Commission, Recommendations, Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Boy Scouts (Box 12)
  - Budget, Director (Box 12)
  - Budget, Advisory Committee (Box 13)
  - Budget, Personnel survey (Box 13)
  - Budget, Personnel survey, Report, Definition of Classes (Box 13-14)
  - Budget, Requests (Box 14)
  - Budget, Requests, From Sheriff (Box 14)
  - Budget, Transportation rate (Box 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Superintendent (Box 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Superintendent, Recommendations, Bates, James B. (Box 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Superintendent, Recommendations, Cease, George M. (Box 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Superintendent, Recommendations, Savedge, W.W. (Box 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Superintendent, Recommendations, Miscellaneous (Box 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Capitol Building (Box 14)
  - Byrd, Richard Evelyn (Box 14)
  - Byrd, William, Portrait (Box 14)
  - Cape Henry Memorial Commission (Box 15)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Richmond (Box 15)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Virginia (Box 15)
  - Chancellorsville (Box 15)
  - Children's Home Society (Box 15)
  - Chinese Ambassador (Box 15)
  - Christmas cards from governors (Box 15)
  - Clerk of the House of Delegates (Box 15)
  - Clerk of the House of Delegates, Recommendations, Greene, George A. (Box 15)
  - Clerk of the House of Delegates, Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Coal (Box 15)
  - Colonial National Monument (Box 15)
  - Comptroller (Box 15)
  - Comptroller, Recommendations, Gathright, A.B. (Box 16)
  - Comptroller, Recommendations, Gilmer, Henry (Box 16)
  - Comptroller, Recommendations, Hunt, D.R. (Box 16)
  - Comptroller, Compensation Board (Box 16)
  - Condolences (Box 16)
  - Confederate Home for Women (Box 6)
  - Confederate Home for Women, Memorial Park (Box 16)
  - Confederate Home for Women, Pensions (Box 16)
  - Connecticut Footguards (Box 16)
  - Conservation and Development, Chairman (Box 16-17)
  - Conservation and Development, Recommendations, Dodson, E. Griffith (Box 17)
  - Conservation and Development, Recomendations, Farriar, T.L. (Box 17)
  - Conservation and Development, Recommendations, Miscellaneous (Box 17)
  - Conservation and Development, Members, Recommendations (Box 17)
  - Conservation and Development, Century of Progress (Box 17)
  - Conservation and Development, Civilian Conservation Corps (Box 17)
  - Conservation and Development, Dept. of Historic Relics (Box 17)
  - Conservation and Development, Jamestown (Box 17)
  - Conservation and Development, Negro Memorial (Box 17)
  - Conservation and Development, Shenandoah National Park (Box 18)
  - Conservation and Development, Shenandoah National Park, Relocation of families (Box 18)
  - Conservation and Development, State Parks (Box 19)
  - Conservation and Development, State Parks, Seashore Park (Box 19)
  - Conservation and Development, States Publicity (Box 19)
  - Conservation and Development, Tourist Bureau (Box 20)
  - Constitutional Sesquicentennial (Box 20-21)
  - Consuls (Box 21)
  - Contributions (Box 21)
  - Corporation Commission (Box 21)
  - Corporation Commission, Aviation (Box 22)
  - Corporation Commission, Banking (Box 22)
  - Corporation Commission, Insurance (Box 22)
  - Corporation Commission, Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 22)
  - Corporation Commission, Public Utility rates (Box 22)
  - Corporation Commission, Refunds of Entrance fees (Box 23)
  - Corporation Commission, Rural electrification (Box 23)
  - Council of State Government (Box 23)
  - County Government, Scott County (Box 23)
  - County Government, Smyth County (Box 23)
  - Corporation Commission, Wise County (Box 23)
  - Crab Industry Committee (Box 23)
  - Crawford case (Box 23)
  - Crime (Box 23)
  - Crime, Office files (Box 24)
  - Davis, Jefferson, Tablet (Box 24)
  - Daylight Savings Time (Box 24)
  - Deeds, Commission of (Box 24)
  - Delegates, Appointed for meetings (Box 24)
  - Delegates, Miscellaneous (Box 24-25)
  - Delegates, Allied Good Roads Convention (Box 25)
  - Delegates, American Association for Labor Legislation (Box 25)
  - Delegates, American Forestry Association (Box 25)
  - Delegates, American Game Conference (Box 25)
  - Delegates, American Library Association (Box 25)
  - Delegates, American Mining Congress (Box 25)
  - Delegates, American Motor Vehicle Administrators (Box 25)
  - Delegates, American Prison Association (Box 25)
  - Delegates, American Psycheatric Association (Box 25)
  - Delegates, American Public Health Association (Box 25)
  - Delegates, Atlantic Deeper Waterways (Box 25)
  - Delegates, Daniel Boone Bicentennial Commission (Box 25)
  - Delegates, Institute of Public Affairs (Box 25-26)
  - Delegates, National Association of State Aviation Officials (Box 26)
  - Delegates, National Conference on Labor Legislation (Box 26)
  - Delegates, National Conference on Social Work (Box 26)
  - Delegates, National Conference on State Parks (Box 26)
  - Delegates, National Conference on Street and Highway Safety (Box 26)
  - Delegates, National Recreation Congress (Box 26)
  - Delegates, River and Harbors Congress (Box 26)
  - Delegates, National Tax Association (Box 27)
  - Delegates, North American Gasoline Tax Conference (Box 27)
  - Delegates, North American Wildlife Conference (Box 27)
  - Delegates, Regional Conference on Labor Legislation and Economic Security (Box 27)
  - Delegates, Regional Conference on Labor Standards (Box 27)
  - Delegates, Second Interstate Assembly (Box 27)
  - Delegates, Southeastern Traffic Conference on States and Highway Safety (Box 27)
  - Delegates, United States Good Roads Association (Box 27)
  - Delegates, Up-Stream Engineering Conference (Box 27)
  - Democratic Campaign (Box 27)
  - Drought relief (Box 27)
  - Dry Cleaners Board (Box 27)
  - Economic Recovery Committee (Box 28)
  - Economy Measures (Box 28)
  - Education, Misc. (Box 28)
  - Education, 1934 (Box 28-29)
  - Education, Superintendents of Public Instruction (Box 29)
  - Education, Board (Box 29)
  - Education, Negro (Box 29)
  - Education, Operating Funds (Box 30)
  - Education, Rehabilitation (Box 30)
  - Education, Reports (Box 30)
  - Education, Teacher Retirement Fund (Box 30)
  - Election, Misc. (Box 30)
  - Election, Democratic Primary (Box 30)
  - Election, Presidential, 1936 (Box 30-31)
  - Election, Writs of Third Congressional District (Box 31)
  - Examining Boards, Accountancy (Box 31)
  - Examining Boards, Accountancy, Recommendations, Jordan, W.P. (Box 31)
  - Examining Boards, Accountancy, Recommendations, Oglethorpe, J.B. (Box 31)
  - Examining Boards, Accountancy, Registration Fee controversy (Box 31)
  - Examining Boards, Bar (Box 31)
  - Examining Boards, Dental (Box 32)
  - Examining Boards, Embalming (Box 32)
  - Examining Boards, Engineers, Architects, and Land Surveyors (Box 32)
  - Examining Boards, Librarians (Box 32)
  - Examining Boards, Medical (Box 32)
  - Examining Boards, Nurses (Box 32)
  - Examining Boards, Optometry (Box 32)
  - Examining Boards, Pharmacy (Box 32)
  - Examining Boards, Pharmacy, Recommendations, Locke, W.E. (Box 32)
  - Examining Boards, Pharmacy, Recommendations, Pollard, C.A. (Box 32)
  - Examining Boards, Pilots, Commissioners to Examine (Box 32)
  - Examining Boards, Veterinary (Box 32)
  - Fairfax, William, Will of (Box 32)
  - Farley dinner (Box 32)
  - Fee Commission (Box 32)
  - Fisheries, Commission (Box 33)
  - Fisheries, Commission, Chairman, Recommendations, Armstrong, Richard (Box 33)
  - Fisheries, Commission, Chairman, Recommendations, Bloxom, O.A. (Box 33-34)
  - Fisheries, Commission, Chairman, Recommendations, Dameron, H.E. (Box 34)
  - Fisheries, Commission, Chairman, Recommendations, Misc. (Box 34)
  - Flags (Box 34)
  - Flood relief (Box 34)
  - Forest wardens (Box 34)
  - Forestry (Box 34)
  - Forfeited automobiles (Box 34)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries (Box 35)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman (Box 35)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Chairman, Recommendations, Nolting, Earl (Box 35)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Game Warden (Box 36)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Members (Box 36)
  - Gasoline tax (Box 36)
  - Geologist, State (Box 36)
  - Gettysburg Celebration (Box 36)
  - Gold (Box 36)
  - Gold Star Mother (Box 36)
  - Governor's Conference (Box 36)
  - Governor's Mansion (Box 36)
  - Governor's Automobiles (Box 37)
  - Governor's Office (Box 37)
  - Governor's Office, Staff (Box 37)
  - Governor's Office, Appointments (Box 37)
  - Gunston Hall (Box 37)
  - Hall of Fame, Bust, Sam Houston (Box 37)
  - Hall of Fame, Bust, Sam Houston, Invitations (Box 37)
  - Hall of Fame, Bust, Stonewall Jackson (Box 37)
  - Hall of Fame, Plates for busts (Box 37)
  - Hall of Fame, Programs (Box 37)
  - Hampton Roads Sewage Disposal Commission (Box 38)
  - Hampton Roads Sewage Disposal Commission, Recommendations (Box 38)
  - Hampton Roads Sewage Disposal Commission, Study (Box 38)
  - Harper's Ferry (Box 38)
  - Health, Commissioner (Box 38)
  - Health, Commissioner, Recommendations (Box 38)
  - Health, Board (Box 38)
  - Health, Bureau of Vital Statistics (Box 38)
  - Health, Sanatoriums, Blue Ridge (Box 39)
  - Health, Sanatoriums, Catawba (Box 39)
  - Health, Sanatoriums, Piedmont (Box 39)
  - Highways, Commissioner (Box 39-40)
  - Highways, Commissioner, Recommendations (Box 40)
  - Highways, Commission to Study Primary Highway System (Box 40)
  - Highways, Lee Highway (Box 40)
  - Highways, Positions (Box 40)
  - Highways, Sky Line Drive (Box 41)
  - Holidays (Box 41)
  - Hospitals, Board (Box 41)
  - Hospitals, Central State, Recommendations (Box 41)
  - Hospitals, Colony (Box 41)
  - Hospitals, Eastern State, Dunbar Farm (Box 41)
  - Huguenot Society (Box 42)
  - Inauguration of Peery, Correspondence, 1933 December (Box 42)
  - Inauguration of Peery, Correspondence, 1934 January (Box 42)
  - Inauguration of Peery, Invitations (Box 42)
  - Inauguration of Peery, Plans for ceremonies (Box 42)
  - Inauguration of Peery, Programs, 1918 (Box 42)
  - Inauguration of Peery, Programs, 1922 (Box 43)
  - Inauguration of Peery, Programs, 1926 (Box 43)
  - Inauguration of Peery, Programs, 1934 (Box 43)
  - Inauguration of Peery, Gubernatorial calling cards (Box 43)
  - Indians (Box 43)
  - Industrial Commission (Box 43)
  - Industries, New (Box 43)
  - Institute of Governments, Public Affairs (Box 43)
  - Insurance Commission (Box 43)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 43)
  - Invitations, Engraved file copies (Box 44)
  - Invitations, Extended (Box 44)
  - Invitations, Received (Box 44-48)
  - Japanese Ambassador (Box 49)
  - Jefferson, Thomas, Memorial Foundation (Box 49)
  - Jems (Box 49)
  - Judges, Designation (Box 49)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Civil Justice Court, Norfolk (Box 50)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Civil Justice Court, Richmond (Box 50)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Corporation Court, Buena Vista and Radford (Box 50)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Corporation Court, Norfolk (Box 50)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Corporation Court, Staunton (Box 50)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Judicial Circuit Court, 11th, Smith, Herbert G. (Box 50)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Judicial Circuit Court, 11th, Weymouth, John (Box 50-51)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Judicial Circuit Court, 13th (Box 51)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Judicial Circuit Court, 27th (Box 51)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Law and Chancery Court, Norfolk, Bragg, S. Burrell (Box 51)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Law and Chancery Court, Norfolk, Parker, William L. (Box 51)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Law and Chancery Court, Norfolk, Shacklefor, O.L. (Box 51)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Law and Chancery Court, Norfolk, Taylor, Walton (Box 52)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Law and Chancery Court, Norfolk, Tyler, S. Heth (Box 52)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Bazile, Leon (Box 52)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Bryan, Albert V. (Box 52)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Buchanan (Box 52)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Chichester, Cassius, Jr. (Box 52)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Clement, J. Turner (Box 52)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Eggleston, John W. (Box 52)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Gunter, Benjamin T. (Box 52)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, McLemore, James L. (Box 53)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Riely, Henry C. (Box 53)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Spratley, C. Vernon (Box 53)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Sutton, Frank T. (Box 53)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Williams, Phillip (Box 53)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Wilson, P.T. (Box 53)
  - Judges, Recommendations, Supreme Courts, Misc. (Box 53)
  - Labor, Commissioner (Box 54)
  - Labor, Commissioner, Recommendations (Box 54)
  - Labor, Reports (Box 54)
  - Labor, State Employment Service (Box 54)
  - Lafayette bust (Box 54)
  - Land grants, Letters to Court Clerks (Box 54)
  - Law enforcement (Box 55)
  - Law enforcement, Bonus marchers (Box 56)
  - Law enforcement, Gambling, Virginia Beach (Box 56)
  - Law enforcement, Johovah's Witnesses (Box 56)
  - Law enforcement, Slot machines (Box 56)
  - Law enforcement, Strikes, Clinches (Box 56)
  - Law enforcement, Strikes, Covington (Box 56)
  - Law enforcement, Strikes, Danville (Box 57)
  - League of Virginia Municipalities (Box 57)
  - League of Women Voters (Box 57)
  - Legion of Valor (Box 57)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Alcoholic Beverage Control Act (Box 57)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Automobile accidents (Box 57)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Banks and Banking (Box 57)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Compensation and Retirement of Judges (Box 57)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Criminal Procedure (Box 57)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Motor Vehicles (Box 57)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Old Age Assistance (Box 58)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Probation and Parole (Box 58)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Purchase and Printing Laws (Box 58)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Social Security (Box 58)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Soil Conservation (Box 58)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Soil Erosion and Conservation (Box 58)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Supreme Court of Appeals (Box 58)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Trial Justice Act of 1934 (Box 58)
  - Legislative Council, Reports, Unemployment Compensation (Box 58)
  - Librarian, Library Building Commission (Box 58)
  - Lists (Box 59)
  - Lynching (Box 59)
  - Madison Celebration (Box 59)
  - Manassas Battlefield Park Inc. (Box 59)
  - Medical College of Virginia (Box 59)
  - Memberships (Box 59)
  - Milk Commission (Box 59-60)
  - Miller School (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, A (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, Alabama, Governor of (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, Arkansas, Governor of (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, B (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, Burch, T.G. (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, C (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, California, Governor of (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous, Connecticut, Governor of (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous, D (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous, Delaware, Governor of (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous, E (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous, F (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous, Florida, Governor of (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous, G (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous, Georgia, Governor of (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous, Glass, Carter (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous, H (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous, I (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, Indiana, Governor of (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, J (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, K (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, Kansas, Governor of (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, Kentucky, Governor of (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, L (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, Louisiana, Governor of (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, M (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, Maine, Governor of (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, Maryland, Governor of (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, Massachusetts, Governor of (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, Missouri, Governor of (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, N (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, New Hampshire, Governor of (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, New Jersey, Governor of (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, New York, Governor of (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, North Carolina, Governor of (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, O (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, Ohio, Governor of (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, Oregon, Governor of (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, P (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, Pennsylvania, Governor of (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, Pollard, John Garland (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, R (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, S (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, South Carolina, Governor of (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous, Swem, Dr. E.G. (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous, T (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous, Tennessee, Governor of (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous, Texas, Governor of (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous, U (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous, V (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous, Vermont, Governor of (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous, W (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous, West Virginia, Governor of (Box 65)
  - Miscellaneous, Wisconsin, Governor of (Box 65)
  - Miscellaneous, X, Y, Z (Box 65)